<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CarbonCalculator</string>

    <string name="menuAboutButton">ABOUT</string>
    <string name="menuCalculatorButton">CALC</string>
    <string name="menuWelcomeMessage">Welcome to the Green Food Challenge!</string>
    <string name="menuAboutDescription">Click here to learn more about\nthe challenge! -></string>
    <string name="menuCalculatorDescription">Click here to learn more about\nthe impact of your diet! -></string>

    <string name="aboutQuitButton">Menu</string>
    <string name="aboutNextPageButton">Next</string>
    <string name="aboutPreviousPageButton">Prev</string>

    <string name="aboutPage1">PAGE 1</string>
    <string name="aboutOverviewTitle">Overview</string>
    <string name="aboutOverviewText">
        As part of the Greenest City Action Plan, Vancouver aims to be the greenest city in the
        world by 2020. One way the city plans to achieve this is by reducing its carbon footprint
        by 33% relative to their 2006 footprint. This app is developed to help users track and
        reduce their carbon footprint in Vancouver.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutFootprintTitle">What is a carbon footprint?</string>
    <string name="aboutFootprintText">
        A carbon footprint refers to the emission of various carbon compounds as a result from using
        or producing products. These emissions contribute toward the greenhouse effect and is measured
        in CO2e (CO2 equivalents). To put Vancouver’s plan in perspective, in 2015, Metro Vancouver’s
        emissions ranged between 6-8 tonnes CO2e per capita, compared to the global sustainable goal
        of reaching 2 tonnes CO2e per capita by 2050.
    </string>

    <string name="aboutPage2">PAGE 2</string>
    <string name="aboutContributionTitle">What contributes to greenhouse gases?</string>
    <string name="aboutContributionText">
        The top two contributing factors for greenhouse gases emissions come from transportation and
        electricity, both sourcing energy by burning fossil fuel. Other major emission sources include
        buildings, food, and consumables and waste.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutEmissionsSource">Source: Vancouver EcoCity Footprint Tool</string>

    <string name="aboutPage3">PAGE 3</string>
    <string name="aboutReductionTitle">What can be done to reduce emissions?</string>
    <string name="aboutReductionText">
        Instead of driving, people can opt to carpool or take transit to reduce fossil fuel consumption.
        Switching from gas to electric whether it be in cars or in heating systems can help as well.
        The carbon emission cost of red meats is significantly higher than white meat, so a change in
        diet will reduce your footprint.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutImpactTitle">Carbon Impact on food</string>
    <string name="aboutImpactText1">
        The reason the two red meats, lamb and beef, have such a high carbon footprint is due to
        the animals’ ability to expel a lot of methane gas from digestion. The gas byproduct from
        cows and lambs comprise 85% of all total methane emissions.\nRead more here:
        https://ec.europa.eu/info/news/eu-agricultural-outlook-european-emissions-linked-agriculture-set-decrease-2030_en
    </string>
    <string name="aboutPage4">PAGE 4</string>
    <string name="aboutImpactText2">
        Below is a chart comparing CO2e production cost of various foods. 90% of Vancouverites in
        the Metro Vancouver area eat  foods high in CO2e. Simply by cutting out red meat consumption
        and replacing it with chicken, as well as reducing total daily meat intake from 35% to 10%,
        can cut down about 1 million tonnes of CO2e per year.
    </string>
    <string name="aboutCO2eCostsSource">Source: https://ec.europa.eu/info/news/eu-agricultural-outlook-european-emissions-linked-agriculture-set-decrease-2030_en</string>
    <string name="aboutPage5">PAGE 5</string>
    <string name="aboutChallengeTitle">Green Food Challenge</string>
    <string name="aboutChallengeText">
        Our challenge is to have participants install our application and to better understand the
        impact their diet has on carbon emissions, as well as discover how dietary changes can reduce
        their carbon footprint.\nIn this app, users track their current meals and their CO2e costs.
        As they transition to more “green meals”, users can observe how many tonnes of CO2e is reduced
        in their footprint as well if everyone in their community made the same changes. Users can
        also share and recommend “low carbon” meals to others in an effort to spread the sustainability movement.
    </string>
    <string name="saving_calculator_description">Slide to see how you can minimize your food carbon footprint.</string>
    <string name="saving_calculator_result">You would save %1$s kg of CO2e in a year with this meal plan. </string>
    <string name="hello">hello</string>
</resources>
